[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone. <br /><br />Click \"Continue\" when you're ready to move on.","rt":50276,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":92878,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</ sub>, yo u start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":10021,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":102904,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":2461,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":105372,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":4077,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":109452,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1122,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":110578,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":3978,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":114558,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1741,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":116302,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":5972,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":122275,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1091,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":123369,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum i s 6 or b igger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":3624,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":126994,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":1202,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":128198,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":5881,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":134081,"internal_chunk_id":"0 -0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":1131,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":135216,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":2894,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":138113,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":1414,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":139531,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember,  to perfo rm +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":2443,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":141975,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1138,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":143115,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":3475,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":146591,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1071,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":147665,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":2742,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":150409,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":853,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":151264,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":17149,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":168419,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the thing that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Sim ilarly,  3 is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":41259,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":209682,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":4058,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":213745,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":983,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":214732,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of a n elemen t is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":4488,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":219222,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1210,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":220435,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2616,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":223054,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Corre ct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1083,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":224138,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":2636,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":226776,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":880,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":227658,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br />< br /> (R emember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":2742,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":230402,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":2818,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":233223,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":2276,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":235501,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We  have on e last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because of this, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":47370,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":282874,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can m ake ever y other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":6483,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":289361,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":1318,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":290683,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":2852,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":293537,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is a g enerator  under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":7337,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":300877,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":2924,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":303806,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</ sub> 4,  and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":1041,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":304851,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":8896,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":313750,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":5710,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":319464,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</s ub>, on  the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":19871,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":339338,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":4103,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":343445,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":977,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":344424,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"W hat is 3  +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":3456,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":347882,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":3384,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":351270,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":4715,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":355988,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":3100,"trial_type":"questio n","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":359092,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":3722,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":362818,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":2981,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":365802,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2594,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":368400,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0 is the identity because it can combine to reproduce every number in the series.","response_history":["0 is the identity because it can combine to reproduce every number in the servies","0 is the identity because it can combine to reproduce every number in the servie","0 is the identity because it can combine to reproduce every number in the servi","0 is the identity because it can combine to reproduce every number in the serv","0 is the identity because it can combine to reproduce every number in the seres.","0 is the identity because it can combine to reproduce every number in the seres","0 is the identity because it can combine to reproduce every number in the sere","0 is the identity because it can combine to reproduce every number in the series."],"rt":44768,"trial_type":"ques tion","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":413171,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":12334,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":425511,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","response_history":["7"],"rt":4208,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":429724,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"6, because 3 + 6 = 9 which will then become 0 again.","response_history":["6, because 3 + 6 = 9 when ","6, b ecause 3  + 6 = 9 when","6, because 3 + 6 = 9 whe","6, because 3 + 6 = 9 which will then become 0 agasin","6, because 3 + 6 = 9 which will then become 0 agasi","6, because 3 + 6 = 9 which will then become 0 agas","6, because 3 + 6 = 9 which will then become 0 again."],"rt":30338,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":460068,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No, because every number from 0 to 8 cannot be created with just 2s.","response_history":["No, because every number from 0 to 8 cannot be created with just 2s."],"rt":21743,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":481816,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No, because every number from 1 to 8 cannot be reproduced with just 3s.","response_history":["No, because every number from 1 to 8 cannot be reproduced with just 3s."],"rt":27666,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":509487,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No, because every number between 0 and 8 cannot be reproduced with just 5s.","response_history":["No, because every number between 0 and 8 cannot be reproduced with just 5s."],"rt":25229,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":534722,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No, because every number between 0 and 8 cannot be reproduced with just 6s.","response_history":["No, because every number between 0 and 8 cannot be reproduced with just 5s.","No, because every number between 0 and 8 cannot be reproduced with just s.","No, because every number between 0 and 8 cannot be reproduced with just 6s."],"rt":8840,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":543568,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use \"+_n\", and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":28498,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":572068,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inv erse of  1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"1 + (n - 1) would be the inverse.","response_history":["1+","1 + (n","1 + (_n -1)","1 + (_n - 1)","1 + (n - 1) w","1 + (n - 1) would be in ","1 + (n - 1) would be in","1 + (n - 1) would be i","1 + (n - 1) would be the inverse."],"rt":59089,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":631160,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"x + (n - x) would be the formula. This equals n, and according to the rules for +n, whenever the total equals n, it reverts back to 0, which is the inverse.","response_history":["x + (n - x) would be the formuol","x + (n - x) would be the formuo","x + (n - x) would be the formula. X ","x + (n - x) would be  the for mula. X","x + (n - x) would be the formula. This equals n, and any","x + (n - x) would be the formula. This equals n, and an","x + (n - x) would be the formula. This equals n, and a","x + (n - x) would be the formula. This equals n, and according to the rules for +n, whenever the total is","x + (n - x) would be the formula. This equals n, and according to the rules for +n, whenever the total i","x + (n - x) would be the formula. This equals n, and according to the rules for +n, whenever the total equals n, it ret","x + (n - x) would be the formula. This equals n, and according to the rules for +n, whenever the total equals n, it reverts back to 0, which is the inverse."],"rt":100805,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":731970,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the el ements?. ","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"If x divides evenly into n it might be a generator.","response_history":["If x dv","If x divides evenly u","If x divides evenly into n it might ba ","If x divides evenly into n it might ba","If x divides evenly into n it might be a generatore.","If x divides evenly into n it might be a generatore","If x divides evenly into n it might be a generator."],"rt":37037,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":769013,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":7863,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":776879,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be  a gener ator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":4118,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":781001,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must divide n.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":12171,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":793175,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"I think only multiples of a divisor of n can be generators, therefore this is false. Otherwise,  every nu mber could not be generated.","response_history":["I think only multiples of n can ","I think only multiples of a divisor of n can bre g","I think only multiples of a divisor of n can bre ","I think only multiples of a divisor of n can bre","I think only multiples of a divisor of n can br","I think only multiples of a divisor of n can be generatore","I think only multiples of a divisor of n can be generators, therefor this is false. Othersi","I think only multiples of a divisor of n can be generators, therefor this is false. Others","I think only multiples of a divisor of n can be generators, therefor this is false. Otherwiese,","I think only multiples of a divisor of n can be generators, therefor this is false. Otherwiese","I think only multiples of a divisor of n can be generators, therefor this is false. Otherwies","I think only multiples of a divisor of n can be generators, therefor this is false. Otherwie","I think only multiples of a divisor of n can be generators, the refor th is is false. Otherwise ","I think only multiples of a divisor of n can be generators, therefor this is false. Otherwise, every number would ","I think only multiples of a divisor of n can be generators, therefor this is false. Otherwise, every number would","I think only multiples of a divisor of n can be generators, therefor this is false. Otherwise, every number woul","I think only multiples of a divisor of n can be generators, therefor this is false. Otherwise, every number wou","I think only multiples of a divisor of n can be generators, therefor this is false. Otherwise, every number wo","I think only multiples of a divisor of n can be generators, therefor this is false. Otherwise, every number w","I think only multiples of a divisor of n can be generators, therefor this is false. Otherwise, every number could not be generated.","I think only multiples of a divisor of n can be generators, therefore this is false. Otherwise, every number could not be generated."],"rt":80641,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":873821,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Never","response_history":["Never"],"rt":35188,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":909012,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"Always, because x + n(x) should always revert to being x again.","response_history":["Always, because x + n(x) should wla","Always, because x + n(x) should wl","Always , becaus e x + n(x) should w","Always, because x + n(x) should always rebert","Always, because x + n(x) should always reber","Always, because x + n(x) should always rebe","Always, because x + n(x) should always reb","Always, because x + n(x) should always revert to being x again."],"rt":75229,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":984246,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Always","response_history":["Always"],"rt":7184,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":991437,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press \"Continue\" to continue.","rt":2248,"trial_type":"instruction s","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":993690,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"49","response_history":["49"],"rt":3650,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":997343,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Some college, no degree","response_history":["Some college, no degree"],"rt":4033,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":1001383,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not  sure wh ich one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Calculus I","response_history":["Beginning Calculus I","Calculus I"],"rt":20261,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":1021647,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","response_history":["2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was"],"rt":6935,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":1028585,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":" multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","response_history":["2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was"],"rt":4407,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":1032995,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - definitely","response_history":["2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"rt":6127,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":1039127,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not  at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":3131,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":1042262,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - definitely","response_history":["3 - definitely"],"rt":2470,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":1044734,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Male","response_history":["Male"],"rt":2283,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":1047019,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your ho usehold  when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","response_history":["English"],"rt":7563,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":1054585,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":5406,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":1059994,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"It was interesting! Math concepts are always a challenge to try and master","response_history":["It was interesting! matc","It was interesting! mat","It was interesting! ma","It was interesting! m","It was interesting! Math son","It was interesting! Math so","It was interesting! M ath s"," It was interesting! Math conces","It was interesting! Math concepts are alwasy","It was interesting! Math concepts are alwas","It was interesting! Math concepts are always interst","It was interesting! Math concepts are always inters","It was interesting! Math concepts are always inter","It was interesting! Math concepts are always inte","It was interesting! Math concepts are always int","It was interesting! Math concepts are always in","It was interesting! Math concepts are always i","It was interesting! Math concepts are always fun","It was interesting! Math concepts are always fu","It was interesting! Math concepts are always f","It was interesting! Math concepts are always a challenge to try and master"],"rt":33526,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":1093524,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"}]